

# Arian Saputra

**Backend Developer** 

## **CORE SKILLS**

**FastAPI** 

Flask

MySql

Linux

**Docker** 

**VueJS** 

**Nginx** 

LXC

Redis

Golang

## **Personal**

22 tahun

rianariansaputra@gmail.com

@rhyanz.rs

github.com/Rhyanz46

+6285337949499

fb.me/rhyanz.rs

linkedin.com/in/rhyanz46

in

Labu Api, Lombok Barat, **Nusa Tenggara Barat** 

## Interest

**DevOps** 

**Networking** 

**Programming** 

Rust, C/C++

#### **Software Architecture**

Microservice, Event Driven, PlugIn

#### **Backend Technology**

Message Broker, Service Registery, Service Mesh, Kubernetes, GRPC, **Elastic Search, Graph Database,** ETC..

#### **About Me**

Hi, I am Backend Engineer. I have experience in software development about 1 half of years, I can build the backend service from scratch until it's deployed. Not only that thing, I am also can work in Frontend field.

I have strong understanding and proficient using framework and programming languages such as Flask, Fastapi, Python, Golang and Javascript, but also can write some simple system using Vue.js, React.js, and Android (Java).

I am very interested on software architecture like Microservices, Event driven and so on.

## **Experience**

2017 - Present

**Freelancer ( Software Engineer )** 

Working on small project like automation script, web apps, android apps and sometimes bug fix on application that has been running before.

#### Tools:

Redis, Docker, LXC, Nginx, Apache, Postgresql, Mysql, Flask, FastApi, Java (Android), Vue.js, Linux, Github, Firebase, Google APIs, GCP, Laravel, Figma, Google Cloud Function, PHP, React.JS, Laravel

2019 - 2020

PT. Netzen Media Akses (Backend Engineer)

Design system and make service based on RestApi for Boats Booking Apps, it just single service (monolith architecture), About 90% it's wrote by me and the rest wrote by my friend.

My Favorite feature that i wrote is:

- Searching for boat that will go to a place with fillter options (by date, boat provider, and so on)
- Payment Gateway service

### Tools:

Nginx, Mysql, Flask, Linux, Github, Google APIs, GCP, Xendit, Midtrans, Docker, Trello

2018 - 2019

**CV. Lumbung Inovasi (Frontend Developer)** 

Building Web Application that provide about Village Information, my responsibility is to consume API from Backend and make it visualization to a Charts, Table, Maps, make struture for my components and so on.

Tools:

Vue.JS, Google Maps API, Youtube API, Linux, Gtilab

## **Education**

2016 - Present

**Bumigora University** 

Information Technology - Software Engineering

2013 - 2016

**State Vocational High School 1 Plampang** 

Consertration on software engineering,

Achievement: Got general champion 3 on final project with Web Apps for Hospital Information